<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" xmlns:moz="http://mozac.org/tools">
    <!-- Privacy Notice-->
    <!-- Privacy Notice title-->
    <string name="privacy_notice_title">About your rights</string>
    <!-- Privacy Notice content-->
    <string name="privacy_notice_content">Before using this application, please carefully read our Personal Information Protection Policy. This policy helps you understand why and how we collect, store, use, and protect your personal information. You can click on Read Full Content for further information.
    \nAccording to the "Regulations on the Scope of Necessary Personal Information for Common Types of Mobile Internet Applications," the Chinese version of Firefox browser belongs to the "browser category," with its basic function being "browsing Internet information resources." No personal information is required to use the basic functions.
    \nBy agreeing to the Personal Information Protection Policy, you acknowledge that you understand the functions provided by the application and the necessary personal information required for the functioning, but this does not mean you agree to our collection of non-essential personal information. For non-essential personal information processing, we will seek your consent separately during your use of the service. Refusing to provide non-essential personal information will not affect your use of basic functions.
    \nWhen you agree to the Personal Information Protection Policy, the related permissions will not be enabled by default. We will enable these permissions after obtaining your consent through a separate pop-up when you use the corresponding functions. You can also close the permissions at any time through device settings. If you disagree with enabling permissions, it will not affect the normal use of other unrelated functions.
    \nClicking "agree" indicates that you have read and agreed to our Personal Information Protection Policy.</string>
    <!-- Privacy Notice clickable-->
    <string name="privacy_notice_clickable1">Read Full Content</string>
    <!-- Privacy Notice positive button-->
    <string name="privacy_notice_positive_button">Agree and Continue</string>
    <!-- Privacy Notice neutral button-->
    <string name="privacy_notice_neutral_button_2">Disagree and Exit</string>

    <!-- Topsites-->
    <!-- Default title for pinned Baidu top site that links to Baidu home page  -->
    <string name="default_top_site_baidu">Baidu</string>
    <!-- Default title for pinned JD top site that links to JD home page  -->
    <string name="default_top_site_jd">JD</string>
    <!-- Default title for pinned JD top site that links to PDD home page  -->
    <string name="default_top_site_pdd">PDD</string>
    <!-- Default title for pinned 58 top site that links to 58 home page  -->
    <string name="default_top_site_tc">58</string>
    <!-- Default title for pinned meituan top site that links to 58 home page  -->
    <string name="default_top_site_meituan">meituan</string>

    <!-- FxA server switch-->
    <!-- Switch Preference for domestic China/global fxa server -->
    <string name="preferences_allow_domestic_china_fxa_server">Use domestic China service</string>
    <!-- Instructions on how to access pairing -->
    <string name="pair_instructions_2_cn"><![CDATA[Scan the QR code shown at <b>firefox.com.cn/pair</b>]]></string>
    <!-- Instructions on how to access pairing -->
    <string name="sign_in_instructions_cn"><![CDATA[On your computer open Firefox and go to <b>https://firefox.com.cn/pair</b>]]></string>

    <!-- Homescreen menu button -->
    <!-- Browser menu button that opens the account setting page -->
    <string name="browser_menu_manage_account_and_devices">Manage Account and Devices</string>
</resources>
